let questions = [
  {
      numb: 1,
      question:"Which is the Wrong way to get an element from HTML in JavaScript?",
      answer: "document.window.ElementById",
      options: [
          "document.getElementById",
         "document.window.ElementById",
          "document.querySelector",
         " document.querySelectorAll"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 2,
      question:"Which Tag is used to connect JavaScript to HTML",
      answer: "script tag",
      options: [
          "scribble tag",
          "JavaScript tag",
          "script tag",
          "java tag"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 3,
      question:"JavaScript uses the following keywords except",
      answer: "Set",
      options: [
          "Let",
          "Const",
          "Var",
          "Set"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 4,
      question:"Which of the folloing operator is known as the JavaScript Assignment Operator",
      answer: "=",
      options: [
          "==",
          "+",
          "++",
          "="
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 5,
      question:"let x = 'Coding' + 1 + 2 + 3; What would be the Output?",
      answer: "Coding123",
      options: [
          "Coding+123",
          "Coding123",
          "Coding6",
          "Coding+6"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 6,
      question:"let x = 7; let y = 9; let z = '7'; What is the output of x === z?",
      answer: "false",
      options: [
          "true",
          "undefined",
          "Nan",
          "false"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 7,
      question:"One of the following is not part of the HTML events that can be used in JavaScript",
      answer: "mousedoubleclick",
      options: [
          "onclick",
          "mousedoubleclick",
          "onmouseover",
          "onmouseout"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 8,
      question:"let chores= ['Sweep', 'Cook', 'Bake', 'Wash', 'Fold Laundry']; chores.pop() equals  ",
      answer: "Fold Laundry",
      options: [
          "Fold Laundry",
          "Wash",
          "Sweer",
          "Cook"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 9,
      question:"const routine = ['Read', 'Netflix', 'Pop-corn', 'Nap']; routine.shift() returns",
      answer: "Netflix, Pop-corn, Nap",
      options: [
          "Read, Netflix, Pop-Corn",
          "Netflix, Pop-corn, Nap",
          "Pop-corn, Nap, Read",
          "Nap, Netflix, Read"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 10,
      question:"JSON stands for?",
      answer: "JavaScript Object Notation",
      options: [
          "JavaScript Subtitle Object Notation",
          "JavaScript Storage Object Notation",
          "JavaScript Object Notation",
          "JavaScript Syntax Object Notation"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 11,
      question:"To onvert a string into a JavaScript Object, we use? ",
      answer: "JSON.parse(text)",
      options: [
          "JSON.stringify(text)",
          "JSON.convert(text)",
          "JSON.parse(text)",
          "JSON.objectify(text)"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 12,
      question:"let x = 69 + '31', typeof x would output ?",
      answer: "string",
      options: [
          "number",
          "variable",
          "string",
          "NaN"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 13,
      question:"1 === '1', True or False",
      answer: "False",
      options: [
          "True",
          "False",
          "Undefined",
          "Boolean"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 14,
      question:"Which symbol is used for comments in JavaScript",
      answer: "//",
      options: [
          "/",
          "//",
          "^/",
          "/^"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 15,
      question:"To return a random number between 0 and 1, We use?",
      answer: "Math.random()",
      options: [
          "Math.random()",
          "Math.Floor()",
          "Math.Int()",
          "Math.decima()"
      ]
  }
  
]